http://www.redcarracing.co.uk/privacy-cookies/

1. Data Protection Act 1998
We comply with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998 when dealing with all data received from visitors to the site.  Under the terms of the Data Protection legislation, we are required to explain to you how we will treat any personal and/or private data which we collect from you.  For more information on the Data Protection Act 1998 you can visit the Information Commissioner’s website.
All our contact details can be found on our website. Follow this link to our contact details
This privacy policy discloses our practices with respect to the collection of information through the Sites and our use of the information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected through this site, and does not apply to information collected through any other sources, including, without limitation, Facebook, Twitter, Instagram and other third party and social media websites.
2. Our Services
We only hold the data necessary to offer services provided on our website.
3. Data Protection Register
Data is only used for the purposes described in our entry on the Data Protection Register.
4. Required Period
We only hold personal data for as long as necessary. Once data is no longer needed it is deleted from our files.
5. Data Storage
For administrative reasons data may be passed to and stored securely with third party service providers located outside the EEA (European Economic Area). Redcar Racecourse Ltd. does not share, sell, or rent personally identifiable information with independent companies for their own use without providing you a choice. Personally identifiable information that you provide to us in the course of using our site features or requesting a product or service through this website may be gathered and stored in one or more of our corporate databases.
6. Email Updates
By registering or placing an order on this website, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy.  We regularly email website news and information updates to those customers who have specifically subscribed to our email service.
All subscription emails sent by us contain clear information on how to unsubscribe from our email service.  Alternatively you can email info@redcarracing.co.uk with "unsubscribe" as the email subject heading and we will remove your email from our mailing list.
7. Our Promise
Redcar Racecourse Ltd. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others.
8. Data Shared With Partners
We may however share commercial and technical data with our partners where a customer has accessed and used our website via a site belonging to one of our partners. However, such information will also be subject to our partners' privacy policies.  Our partners include, without limitation, CGC Events, Future Ticketing, Go Racing In Yorkshire, The Tote, and Racing TV.
9. Email Options
If you subscribe to our email service via a partner site, that partner may wish to send you details via email of other products and services, which may be of interest to you. However when you subscribe directly to our email service you will be asked whether or not you wish to receive such emails.
10. Partner Privacy Policies
Please note that we only share data with partners that operate their own privacy policy.
11. Spam
In accordance with the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, we never send bulk unsolicited emails, (popularly known as Spam) to email addresses.
12. Product Updates
We may send emails to existing customers or prospective customers who have enquired or registered with us, regarding products or services directly provided by us.
13. Email Content
All emails sent by us will be clearly marked as originating from us. All such emails will also include clear instructions on how to unsubscribe from our email service and any future emails. Such instructions will either include a link to a page to unsubscribe or a valid email address to which you should reply, with "unsubscribe" as the email subject heading.
14. Cookies
Our website uses "cookies" to track user's movement, gather broad dempgraphic information and allow customers to purchase from our website. These cookies are not linked to personally identifiable information - they do not contain or pass any personal, confidential or financial information, or any other information that could be used to identify individual visitors or customers purchasing from our website.
Please note that you are free to refuse cookies. However, for purely technical reasons this may prevent you from purchasing from our website. This is because anonymous cookies are commonly used to keep track of the contents of customers' shopping baskets or trolleys during the checkout process. This facility ensures that the items added to (or removed from) your basket are accurately stated when you go to pay.
15. Media & Photography
Spectators and guests are encouraged and permitted to film and record any events and publish any content on any media subject to the following condition: by filming and recording such content You agree that Redcar shall have a perpetual, royalty free, sub-licensable and worldwide licence to use such content in whole or in part in any online or offline promotional, advertising or publicity material or in any format and for any purpose whatsoever, including (but not limited to) TV packages, online players, YouTube, Facebook, Snapchat, Twitter, Vine, Instagram and Dailymotion. Redcar acknowledges that You shall retain ownership of copyright in the content.
Where you are purchasing admission for a Redcar event you acknowledge that at such events photographs and moving images may be taken by Redcar or by others acting on Redcar’s behalf as well as by other members of the public and that your image may be included either deliberately or accidentally in such photographs and moving images. By purchasing tickets for a Redcar Event or by attending such event you agree to release and assign to Redcar permission to licence all images, whether still or moving, and to use such images, as well as any associated sound recordings, in any media for any purpose which may include, amongst others, reporting, advertising, promotion, marketing and publicity for any product, service or future event. You agree that any images may be combined with other images, graphics or text (including your name), cropped, edited altered or modified. You further agree that Redcar will have all rights to such images and associated sound recordings in perpetuity and you acknowledge and agree that Redcar is not liable for any further payment, consideration, accounting or further claim for any reason.
16. Changes to our privacy policy
Any changes to our privacy policy in the future will be posted to the website and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.
17. Contact
All our contact details can be found on our website. Follow this link to our contact details
All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to info@redcarracing.co.uk
You are entitled to see the information held about you and may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us at info@redcarracing.co.uk. We are entitled by law to charge a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
Please use the following link to view our full Data Management and Privacy Policy.
Back to top
